(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T21:58:03.974663",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
レックー動作確認！
Deck check!
始ーまったよー！始ーまったよー！
It's started! It's started!
本日ー！
Today...
何をするのかと言うと！
What are we doing today, you ask?
ホロライブ夏祭りです！
It's the Hololive Summer Festival!
イエーイ！
Yay!
それではまず、お店屋さん紹介をして行きたいと思います！
So first, we'd like to introduce the festival stalls!
えー、まずはー、えー
Uh, first off, um...
レックー動作確認屋...
The Deck Check Stall...
あ、レックー来た！
Oh, here comes the deck!
レックー！
Deck!
こちらは、ハコス流しそうめん屋さんです！
This is Hakos's Flowing Noodles Stall!
いらっしゃい、いらっしゃい！
Step right up, step right up!
いらっしゃい！
Step right up!
いらっしゃい、いらっしゃい！
Step right up, step right up!
流しそうめん、準備してありまししたー！
The flowing noodles are all ready!
ナイス！
Nice!
今日はね、ハコスがね、もう大量のそうめんを一人で茹でてくれたんで！
Today, Hakos boiled a huge batch of noodles all by herself!
すごーい！
Amazing!
はい、そうめん食べたい方はこちら！
Yes, if you want noodles, come here!
そして、ヨーヨー屋さんもあります！
And we also have a Yo-Yo Stall!
ヨーヨー屋さんですか？
Who's running the Yo-Yo Stall?
ヨーヨー屋の白上です！
It's Shirakami at the Yo-Yo Stall!
ヨーヨーあります！
We've got yo-yos!
はい、ということでヨーヨーしたい方はフブキちゃんに声かけてください！
All right, so if you want to play with yo-yos, call out to Fubuki-chan!
そして！
And next!
今、スバルの綿あめ屋さんとなっているんですけど
Right now it says Subaru's Cotton Candy Stall,
今日、綿あめ屋さんをしてくれるのはこの人！
but the person making cotton candy today is this person!
はーい！
Hi~!
うち、うち、うちだよ！大神ミオだよ！
It's me, it's me, it's me! Ookami Mio!
初めて綿あめ作るけど大丈夫かな？よろしくお願いします！
It's my first time making cotton candy, but I hope it goes well! Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします！
Welcome!
イエーイ！
Yay!
やったー！
商そしてですね、他にもですね
And also, besides these...
食べ物がたくさん！たこ焼きとか焼きそばとかね
There's lots of food! Like takoyaki and yakisoba...
りんご飴とかあるんで、好きに食べてください！
and candy apples, so please help yourselves!
イエーイ！
Yay!
そして、今来てくれているメンバー、まず紹介します！
And now, let me introduce the members who are here with us!
まずは、カリ！
First up, Calli!
みなさん！森カリオペです！
Hello everyone! It's Mori Calliope!
よろしくお願いします！
Glad to be here!
やったー！夏大好きー！
Yay! I love summer!
ネリッサ！
Nerissa!
Hi darling! It's Hololive English Advent's double diva, the one and only Nerissa Ravencroft, darls!
ウロドラー！
Urodora!
誰から行く？
Who's going first?
せーの、KEEP GOING!
Ready, set, KEEP GOING!
ウロドラー！
Urodora!
はい、ということで、こんな感じでね
Alright then, so like this,
全体見る担当の大空スバルです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Oozora Subaru, in charge of overseeing everything! Nice to meet you!
はい！それでは、好きに楽しんでください！
Alright! Well then, please enjoy yourselves as you like!
わちゃわちゃやってこう
Let's mess around and have fun!
オッケー、オッケー！わかった！
Okay, okay! Got it!
えっと、何色？
Um, what color?
黄色！ 赤！
Yellow! Red!
足りませんて！
We don't have enough!
自分やってみたいよね
You want to try it yourself, right?
わちゃわちゃするんですけど、夏のわちゃわちゃを楽しんでいってください！
It's gonna be chaotic, but please enjoy the summer chaos!
やったことないから
Because I've never done it before.
初めてなの？
Is it your first time?
ヨーヨー取るぞー！
I'm gonna get a yo-yo!
イカみたいなのいる！
There's one that looks like a squid!
光るやつなんだ
Oh, it's one that lights up.
待って！ 色がない！
Wait! There's no color!
緑、緑！
Green, green!
あー、見えない、見えない！
Ah, I can't see, I can't see!
流れてきた！
It flowed down!
ごめんなさい！
I'm so sorry!
誰かが汁こぼして... I'm so sorry!
Someone spilled the broth... I'm so sorry!
大丈夫、大丈夫！
It's okay, it's okay!
大丈夫だ、トワちゃん
It's alright, Towa-chan.
水色！
Light blue!
大丈夫！ どうにかなる！
It's okay! It'll work out somehow!
あ、きた！ 水色ー！
Ah, here it comes! Light blue!
ここからここから！ 美味しくなるから！
From here, from here! Because it'll get delicious!
ありがとう！ ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
取れました！
I got it!
取れないとかあるの？ 1個もらえよ！
Can you actually fail? Just take one!
うるさい！
Shut up!
フブキ先輩やってみてくださいよ
Fubuki-senpai, why don't you try it?
じゃあ1個あげよう、これ！
Then I'll give you one of these!
いい、大丈夫！
No, it's okay!
ほら、フブキの1個好きなの
Look, take one of Fubuki's that you like!
どれにするの？
Which one will you pick?
すいちゃんが絶対緑か水色選ぶから...
Because Sui-chan will definitely pick green or light blue...
水色！
Light blue!
でも貰います！
But I'll take it!
釣れたー！
I caught it!
釣れたよー！
I caught one!
じゃあそれ貰うじゃん
Then I'll take that one.
釣れました！
I caught it!
何ですか？
What is it?
なんか見えない糸みたいなの出てくるからね
Because like, invisible threads start coming out, you know?
見えない糸？！ 見えない糸って何ー？！
Invisible threads?! What do you mean, invisible threads?!
こわっ！
How scary!
可愛いー！
So cute!
え、流して！
Eh, let it flow!
流します！
Flowing now!
行け、行け！
Go, go!
誰もキャッチできない
No one can catch it!
待って、あるよ！
Wait, it's there!
見えない糸！
Invisible threads!
違う、違う！
No, no!
来い、来い！
Come on, come on!
あったかいよ、この辺
It's warm around here!
綿あめできた！
The cotton candy is ready!
テストでは、テストでは出来てた！
In the test, it was working in the test!
あったかくなるまで時間かかるから！
Because it takes time until it gets warm!
あ、あったかくなってきた！
Ah, it's getting warm!
ナイス、ナイス！
Nice, nice!
お砂糖入れてから回すの？
Do you turn it on after putting the sugar in?
そう！
Yes!
行きます！
Here goes!
あ、怖い、怖い！
Ah, scary, scary!
溶けてない！
It hasn't melted!
まだ、まだ！
Not yet, not yet!
もう一回！
One more time!
さっきの機械のせいにしてさ、出てきた
Blaming it on the machine earlier, but it came out!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
切れない！
I can't cut it!
このオレンジ欲しい！
I want this orange one!
ちょうだい！
Give it to me!
取れた、取れた！
I got it, I got it!
やばい！
Crazy!
外、外！
Outside, outside!
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Hang in there, hang in there!
来た、来た！
Here it comes, here it comes!
いいよ、いいよ！
Good, good!
めっちゃめちゃ上手い！
You're super good!
行け、行け！
Go, go!
来てる、来てる！
It's coming, it's coming!
マジで？！
Seriously?!
お代わり！
Seconds, please!
お代わり行く？
Going for seconds?
お前、邪魔すんなよ！
Hey, don't get in the way!
見て、来た！
Look, it came!
うわー、ナイス！
Woah, nice!
やめて、やめて！
Stop, stop!
ダメ！
No!
やめてー！
Stop it!
ダメー！
Nooo!
ダメ！ ダメ！
No! No!
ネリッサ、ネリッサ！
Nerissa, Nerissa!
ネリッサは好きなのどうぞ！
Nerissa, go ahead and pick whichever you like!
良かったー！
Thank goodness!
可愛い！
So cute!
かっこいい！頑張れ！
So cool! You can do it!
ちょっと待って！逃げないで！
Wait a minute! Don't run away!
いいよ、いいよ！
Nice, nice!
いらっしゃい！いらっしゃい！
Welcome! Welcome!
いらっしゃいませー！
Welcome!
あー！ダメダメダメ！
Ah! No, no, no!
ちょっと待って、これ妙な...
Wait a second, this is kind of weird...
すごい！挑戦！挑戦！
Awesome! Challenge! Challenge!
赤点！赤点！
Failing grade! Failing grade!
あ、イカだ！
Ah, it's a squid!
危ない、危ない！
Dangerous, dangerous!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Hang in there! Hang in there!
You can do it!
何で？何で？いただきます！
Why? Why? Thanks for the food!
待って！ベイビー頑張れ！
Wait! Bae-baby, hang in there!
行ける！行けるよ！
You can do it! You've got this!
浮いてる、浮いてる！
It's floating, it's floating!
あ、ごめんなさい！
Ah, I'm sorry!
やばい！ふむちゃん大丈夫？
Oh no! Is Fumu-chan okay?
ふーちゃん！I'm so sorry!
Fu-chan! I'm so sorry!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ちょっと待って！あ、違う！
Wait a minute! Ah, wrong one!
死ぬんだよ！絶対死ぬ！
You'll die! Definitely gonna die!
あ、オッケー！
Ah, okay!
オッケー！よかった！
Okay! Phew, thank goodness!
わたあめこんなに巻いてる...
The cotton candy is wrapping so much...
ちょっと怖い...
It's a little scary...
美味しい！Let's go!
Delicious! Let's go!
そうめんの所にわたあめ流さないでよ！
Don't slide cotton candy down where the somen is!
何でだよ！流れてる！
Why not?! It's flowing!
待って待って！流さないで！
Wait, wait! Don't let it flow!
髪の毛が...あ、取れた！
The hair is... Ah, got it!
ふわり！ふわりだよ！
Fluffy! It's so fluffy!
任せて！美味しい？
Leave it to me! Is it good?
うまい！もう一回！
Delicious! One more time!
ふむちゃんヨーヨー上手だな！
Fumu-chan is so good at yo-yo!
流しまーす！
Flowing now~!
ベイビーの全部取ってやる！
I'm scooping all of Bae-baby's!
お父さん頑張って！
Do your best, Papa!
先輩！ごめん！
Senpai! Sorry!
おー！これすごい！
Ooh! This is amazing!
うわー、やばい！
Woah, crazy!
やったー！勝ったー！
Yay! I won!
やってる？やってないよ！
Are you cheating? No, I'm not!
絶対やってる！
You're definitely cheating!
あ！逃げられた！
Ah! It got away!
ちゃんとやってないってところを見せるやで！
I'll show you I'm not doing anything shady!
うまい！これやってます！
Yummy! She's definitely cheating!
やってます！やめてー！
She's cheating! Stop it~!
リオナ死んだらあかん！
Riona, don't die!
頑張れ！早く！
Hang in there! Hurry!
あ！見つけた！早く！
Ah! Found it! Quickly!
これ何なんだよ！
What is this supposed to be?!
ビビり！マジで？
Scaredy-cat! For real?
えー！流れてきた！
Ehh! It flowed down!
完成形やばい！
The final form is insane!
自慢してんじゃないよ！
Don't brag about it!
流してー！そっちじゃない！
Flow it~! Not that way!
あー！凄い！
Ah! Amazing!
そうめんはみんなありますよー！
There's somen for everyone~!
頑張れ！ピカチュウの前で...
You can do it! In front of Pikachu...
行け！誰かわたあめ持ってる？
Go! Does anyone have cotton candy?
ふたりのわたあめ...
The cotton candy for two...
ここまで行けるの？
Can it go this far?
締め直して強度を上げるべきや！
We should tighten it to increase durability!
水分が足りない！
It needs more moisture!
ダメダメダメ！
No, no, no!
あ、来たー！ベイビーのそれ！
Ah, here it comes! That's Bae-baby's!
あ、全部取られた！
Ah, she took it all!
ニコに全部取られた！
Niko took everything!
お前わたあめ似合わんなー！
Cotton candy really doesn't suit you!
一口食べてみ...
Take a bite...
食べてるー！美味しい！
I'm eating it! Delicious!
ビビり！いただきますよ！
Scaredy-cat! Digging in!
Easy! Easy!
本当か？ありあり！
Really? Totally fine!
美味しい！美味い！
Delicious! Yummy!
みんな流してー！
Everyone, flow it~!
そうめん食べる前に...速い！
Before eating somen... Fast!
お父さん！頑張れー！
Papa! Do your best~!
早く！早く！
Hurry! Hurry!
お前切りすぎるなよ！
Don't cut too much off!
タイマー回るからね！
Because the timer is running!
やってー！やばい！
Do it~! Oh no!
時間が...！
Time is running out...!
やったー！完成！
Yay! Finished!
可愛い！
So cute!
すごい！すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
いい感じ！
Looking good!
マレンドゥ！ - マレンドゥじゃない！
Marendu! - It's not Marendu!
マレンドゥー！
Marendu!
うわー！すごい！
Woah! That's awesome!
ビビちゃん！
Bibi-chan!
え、どっちが選ばれてるの？
Wait, which one was chosen?
紫にする？
Should we go with purple?
マレンドゥ行きます！
Marendu, going in!
なんだよそれ！
What is that?!
うま！上手い！
Nice! So good!
なんで一回で完成してんの？
Why did it turn out complete in one go?
感覚だよ！ - いいじゃん！
It's all instinct! - Looks great!
頑張れ！
Do your best!
ビビ？ - うまい！
Bibi? - Nice!
え、何？ - すごい！
Huh, what? - Awesome!
うわー！
Woah!
何それ？
What's that?
取れた方がいいの？
Is it better to catch it?
おいおい！誰かこの町内会をセッティングして！
Hey hey! Someone organize this neighborhood association!
それすごい！ - イェーイ！
That's crazy! - Yay!
イェーイ！
Yay!
取れた！
Got it!
可愛いー！
So cute!
上手ー！
So skillful!
チェリー？めっちゃ位置低い。
Cherry? It's really low.
チェリー！メリッサちゃん！
Cherry! Melissa-chan!
そうめん！
Soumen!
イェーイ！
Yay!
大混乱！
Total chaos!
ビビとそうめんだよ！
It's Bibi and soumen!
めちゃ可愛い！
Super cute!
はい！あけがわよ！
Here! Opening!
行くわよー！
Here I go!
キャー！
Kyaa!
うわー！
Woah!
一本！一本しか取れてない！
One strand! You only got one strand!
準備いいですかー？流しますよー！
Are you ready? Sending it down!
負けない！負けない！
Not gonna lose! Not gonna lose!
イェーイ！
Yay!
あれ？フブちゃん？ - ビビのほうが多い！
Huh? Fubu-chan? - Bibi has more!
ヨーヨー釣りよ！
It's yo-yo fishing!
あれ？
Huh?
nobody clear!
Nobody cleared!
取れた！ - うまい！
Got it! - Nice!
やばい！やばい！
Oh no! Oh no!
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
ビビちゃんこうやって食べてる間に...
While Bibi-chan is eating like this...
うまい！
Nice!
光る！光る！
It lights up! It lights up!
じゃあふーちゃんお願いします！
Then, Fuu-chan, please go ahead!
調整ね！取りやすいように！
Adjusting it so it's easier to catch!
取りやすいように調整して...
Adjusting so it's easy to catch...
あー！
Ah-!
ごめん！ごめん！
Sorry! Sorry!
何これー！
What is this-!
綿あめが！
The cotton candy!
あー！つかめた！
Ah! Got a hold of it!
頑張れ！
Hang in there!
オッケー！ゲット！ゲット！
Okay! Got it! Got it!
これゲットー！
Got this one-!
すげー！
Awesome!
取れてないんですけどー！
I didn't get any though-!
ファーストタイムクリアー！
First time clear!
うまい！
Nice!
ピカピカ！
Sparkly!
ナイス！
Nice!
いいと思うけどね。
I think it's good though.
流しそうめん！
Nagashi soumen!
ハンバーガー！
Hamburger!
おいしー！
Delicious!
オッケー！
Okay!
めっちゃ被りついてる！
She's biting into it so hard!
やったー！勝ったー！
Yay! I won!
あ、すごい！
Ah, awesome!
ビブちゃん、すごいよ！
Biboo, that's amazing!
ハンバーガー、ピザ、アイス！
Hamburger, pizza, ice cream!
またね！
See you later!
ねるねるねるね
Neru Neru Nerune!
バイバイ～！
Bye-bye~!
楽しかった！
That was so much fun!
はい、レッツゴー！
Okay, let's go!
すごい！
Awesome!
あ、すごい！
Ah, amazing!
巻いて巻いて巻いて！
Spin it, spin it, spin it!
やめて～！
Stop it~!
あれ？壊れてない？
Huh? Isn't it broken?
頑張って作ってくれ！
Do your best and make it!
あ、黄緑になった！
Ah, it turned yellow-green!
めっちゃつらい！
This is so tough!
虫作ってる！
She's making a bug!
ハンバーガー！
Hamburger!
熱い熱い熱い！
It's hot, hot, hot!
上手上手！
You're so good at this!
進化形作ってる！
She's making an evolved form!
いま言ったの？
Did you just say that?
アメみたいなやつ...
Something like candy...
はい、完成！
Okay, finished!
なんかメロンパンの味がする！
It tastes kind of like melon bread!
なんか美味しい！
It actually tastes good!
なんかバナナ...
Kind of like banana...
ヤバいやばい、これ！
This is crazy!
上手い、上手い！
Nice, nice!
職人やん、手つきが！
You look like a pro with those hands!
やだやだやだ！
No, no, no!
痛くない！
It doesn't hurt!
めっちゃお迎えでヤバい！
The welcome is crazy!
So, we're gonna...
やだ～！
No way~!
流しそうめん食べる！
I'm eating the flowing somen!
配信しない！
I won't stream!
行くよ～！
Here I go~!
電子レンジヤバい！
The microwave is crazy!
ポップキャンディ！
Pop candy!
I will take over.
あだだだだ！
Adadadada!
あ、回った！
Ah, it spun!
危ない、危ない！
Dangerous, dangerous!
Easy!
そして電子レンジ！
And then, the microwave!
結構疲れる！ヤバい！
This is pretty tiring! Crazy!
でも楽しい！
But it's fun!
わー！すごい！
Wow! Awesome!
クルクルしてきた！
It's spinning round and round!
クルクルして！
Spin it round!
またね～！
See you later~!
出来てる！
It's forming!
綿あめ持って帰っていった
She took the cotton candy home.
夏だからね、雰囲気だけでもね
It's summer, so just for the vibe!
あ、スバルも食べたい！
Ah, Subaru wants to eat too!
もうちょっと、もうちょっと！
A bit more, a bit more!
え、すごい！ねねさん！
Whoa, incredible, Nene-san!
フワフワ！
Fluffy!
I'm making a mess.
本当だ！難しくない？
True! Isn't this hard?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
Really big hamburger, please!
オッケーです！ちょっと待ってください！
Okay! Please wait a moment!
あ、出てきた、出てきた！
Ah, it's coming out, coming out!
うわー、グルグルクルクル！
Whoa, spinning round and round!
回る回る！
It spins, it spins!
危ない、危ない！
Careful, careful!
ここ、ここ！上手い！
Here, here! Nice!
オッケー、オッケー！
Okay, okay!
このあとみおちゃんのワンワンがある！
After this is Mio-chan's barking segment!
時間あるから頑張る！
We still have time, so I'll do my best!
10時半からはミオさんのかんかんです！
Mio's stream starts at 10:30!
オッケー、オッケー！
Okay, okay!
大吉だ！大吉が出た！
It's excellent luck! I got excellent luck!
このへんでくるくる...
Twirling around here...
待って待って！待って待って！
Wait, wait! Wait, wait!
おおー！すごい！
Ooh! Awesome!
すごい！楽しい！
Awesome! This is so fun!
控えめに言って最高！
To put it mildly, this is the best!
もっと大きい！めっちゃさあ...
Even bigger! It's super...
夏祭りしたかった！
I wanted to go to a summer festival!
夏祭り感ある！
It really feels like a summer festival!
ホロライブで夏祭りできて最高！
Doing a summer festival in Hololive is the best!
夏祭り行ったことない...
I've never been to a summer festival...
でもこれ以上出ない！
But no more will come out!
そうなの！？ヤバいじゃん！
Is that so!? That's crazy!
コップも回っていけない、これ！
The cup can't even spin like this!
まあまあまあ、大丈夫。一応そうめん屋...
Well, it's fine. It's technically a somen shop...
本当？そうめん屋なんだ！
Really? So it is a somen shop!
そうめん屋なんです。
Yes, it's a somen shop.
え、待って！ビジューめっちゃ上手くない！？
Wait, isn't Bijou super good at this!?
オッケー、オッケー！もうちょっと行こうか、もうちょっとね。
Okay, okay! Let's do a bit more, just a little bit.
ビジューめっちゃ上手いやん！
Bijou is ridiculously good at this!
上手い、上手い！
Nice, nice!
すみません、じゃあそうめんください！
Excuse me, then please give me some somen!
お願いします！
Please!
えー、じゃあ流すよ！
Okay, I'm sending it down!
くるくるくるくる...
Round and round...
おおー！
Ooh!
行くよー！
Here it comes!
イエーイ！おおー！
Yay! Ooh!
オッケー！
Okay!
ヤバい、これピカチュウで詰まるんだよね、いつも。
Oh no, it always gets stuck on Pikachu.
キャー！取れた！
Eek! I caught it!
すごい！ありがとう！
Amazing! Thank you!
これあとで食べます！いただきます！
I'll eat this later! Bon appetit!
Very nice! Very nice!
美味い！
Delicious!
すごーい！
Amazing!
えー！美味い！ビジュー！
Eh! Delicious! Bijou!
ビジュー、ヨーヨー釣りも全部上手いやん！
Bijou, you're so good at yo-yo fishing too!
すげー！上手くてよかった！
Awesome! I'm glad you're good at it!
そうめん食べる？食った！
Want to eat somen? I ate it!
うん、食べます！
Yeah, I'll eat!
え、ネリッサのさ、ビジュー...スバルが流すからさ、食べない？
Hey, Nerissa... Subaru is streaming, so why don't we eat?
2人でさ、一緒にさ...
The two of us, together...
いいの？やっておじ！
Is it okay? Let's do it!
しょうがないな...
Guess we have to...
食べたい？食べて！
Do you want to eat? Eat!
食べる？いいよ！
Eating? Sure!
これ食べていいよ！
You can eat this!
みんなにここで見せる？
Shall we show everyone here?
みんなー！ほらー！
Everyone! Look!
ビジューのコットンキャンディです！
It's Bijou's cotton candy!
わたあめ！わたあめ！
Cotton candy! Cotton candy!
ビジューが取ったヨーヨーも見せて！
Show the yo-yo that Bijou got too!
ほら！
Look!
これ光るからね！光るから！
Because this glows! It glows!
すごいやん、ビジュー！ナイスナイス！
That's awesome, Bijou! Nice, nice!
じゃあビジュー、今から流しそうめん...
Then Bijou, now for the nagashi somen...
じゃあこれ一旦...オッケー！
Then let's put this aside for a bit... Okay!
これ置く場所欲しいね。
We need a place to set this down.
ネリッサが...あ、見て！
Nerissa is... Ah, look!
どこに捨てちゃったの、これ！？ありがとうございます！
Where did you throw this away!? Thank you very much!
ギャー！ネリッサ食べんといて！
Gyaa! Nerissa, don't eat that!
それビジューのコットンキャンディ...
That's Bijou's cotton candy...
食べたい！んー、美味いです！
I want to eat it! Mm, it's delicious!
美味い！？ネリッサわたあめ作った？
Delicious!? Nerissa, did you make cotton candy?
You try? はい！
You try? Yes!
わたあめは美味しいです！
Cotton candy is delicious!
わたあめ美味しい！でも私のスキルですわ！
Cotton candy is delicious! But that's thanks to my skill!
あはは！ちょっと下手です。
Ahaha! It's a bit unskillful.
あ、なるほどね！はいはい！楽しめばいいからね！
Ah, I see! Right, right! As long as you enjoy it!
あ、ミオちゃんも...何その...
Ah, Mio-chan too... What is that...
刺身！これわたあめ作ったら出来た！
Sashimi! I made this while making cotton candy!
ねぇ...汚い、なんか！
Hey... it looks kind of dirty!
なんか...よし！
Kind of... Alright!
なんか嫌だ。それ見せてあげて、ちょっと。
I kind of don't like it. Show that to them for a bit.
じゃあこれ...意外と高画質。
Then this... Surprisingly high quality.
デッカい方のが高画質か。
So the bigger one is higher quality.
嫌だ！それやめて！
No! Stop that!
やめてよー！やめてよ！見せないで、それ！
Stop it~! Stop it! Don't show that!
わたあめの欠片...ミオちゃん！
A piece of cotton candy... Mio-chan!
はい！わたあめ流すのやる、一緒に？
Yes! Do you want to try sending cotton candy down together?
わたあめは流さないで！
Don't send cotton candy down!
ごめん、わたあめは流さない！
Sorry, we won't send cotton candy down!
そうめんを流すのですが、やりますか？
We're going to send somen down, do you want to do it?
やるか！うちも食べたことないから！
Let me try! I've never eaten it before either!
そうめん流しな！よし、それじゃあ行くよ！
Nagashi somen, right! Alright, here we go then!
ちょっと待って！タレない！タレない、うち！
Wait a second! I don't have sauce! I don't have dipping sauce!
タレ作って！そこにあるから！おいじゃあ...
Make some sauce! It's right over there! Okay then...
よいしょ、作りました！
Yoisho, I made it!
懐かしい！なんか我が家でやったときもさ...
Nostalgic! Like when we did it at our house...
周りの水こうなったなってめっちゃ思う！
I distinctly remember the surrounding water getting like this!
でしょ？マジこんなんだったよね！
Right? It was totally like this!
そう！めちゃくちゃこうでした！
Yeah! It was completely like this!
じゃあ... Oh, it's so wet!
Well then... Oh, it's so wet!
Yeah. Oh, be careful of this.
Yes, okay. じゃあ行くよ、2人とも！
Yes, okay. Alright, here goes, you two!
イエーイ！You can do it!
Yay! You can do it!
You can do it! いけ、スコ！
You can do it! Go for it, Suko!
Wow! Can I take it from anywhere?
Yeah! Oh, I can!
Did you catch it? Ha!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Do your best! Do your best!
Nice catch, Bae! イエーイ！
Nice catch, Bae! Yay!
行くよ！ Your turn, your turn!
Here I go! Your turn, your turn!
来い！頑張れ！
Come on! Do your best!
おおー！上手い！
Ooh! Nice catch!
行くよー！ More! More!
Here I go! More! More!
More! More! More!
もっとー！もっとー！
More~! More~!
はい、どうぞー！
Here you go~!
よいしょ！キャー！
Yoisho! Kyaa!
キャー！すごい！
Kyaa! Amazing!
上手いやんビジュー！でも上手い上手い！
You're so good at this, Bijou! But nice, nice!
これだ、これ！ / いやいやいや！
That's it, that's it! / No, no, no!
ダメダメダメ！
No, no, no!
それズルだよ、みおちゃん！
That's cheating, Mio-chan!
それダメー！
You can't do that!
これママ、ママが食べるの、これ！
Mama's going to eat this one!
いや、こっちね、みおちゃん。参加する人こっちね、ここ。
No, over here, Mio-chan. Participants go here.
はい、じゃあもう一回ね。
All right, let's try again.
Go! 行くよ、Go!
Go! Here it comes, go!
No! あー！でもセーフ！
No! Ah, but safe!
あ、いいやん、いいやん！
Oh, nice, nice!
ナイス！あざっす！
Nice! Thank you!
Try! Try! Try! / こっち、こっち。
Try! Try! Try! / Over here, over here.
あ、みお先輩、一回！
Ah, Mio-senpai, one try!
Mio turn! Mio turn!
Mio's turn! Mio's turn!
来い！来い！ホッ！
Come on! Come on! Ha!
おー！いいやん！
Oh! Nice!
うわ、うねー！うめー！
Whoa, smooth! Delicious!
フワモコ来た！
FuwaMoco is here!
すごい、お祭りが！
Wow, a festival!
お！上手い！上手い！
Oh! You're good! So good!
美味しい！でも...
Delicious! But...
Melt? What is it? / 溶けてる、溶けてる。
Melt? What is it? / It's melting, it's melting.
溶けてる！
It's melting!
Look, I made that. I made this one.
これ、ビブーが作ったんだよ。
Bijou made this one, you know!
え、すごい！ビブちゃんが！
Eh, awesome! Bijou-chan did?!
どうぞ！
Here you go!
And I won this!
何それ？ / I won this!
What's that? / I won this!
これこれ、フワモコ、どうぞ！
Here, here, FuwaMoco, go ahead!
大丈夫？あ、大丈夫？オッケー、オッケー！
Is it okay? Ah, okay? Okay, okay!
じゃあフワモコ、これ食べて！
Well then, FuwaMoco, eat this!
えー！りんご飴！そう！
Eh! Candy apples! Yes!
すごい！めちゃ祭りだよ！
Amazing! It really feels like a festival!
いくらさせるの？！ハマって、ハマって！
How much are you charging?! It's stuck, it's stuck!
No, no... Biboo, how much is this?
How much? How much is the cost?
Put in the money? Yeah, I have money.
いくら位する？
How much is it around?
1,000? 1,000 yen!
1,000円？
1,000 yen?
100? 100? 流します。
100? 100? Sending it down.
流してくれる？
Will you send it down?
100万？！100万？！
1 million?! 1 million?!
100万？！流します！
1 million?! Sending it down!
えー、じゃあビブーさん、上手いから流しにまた流してあげて。
Well then, Biboo is so good at it, so send another one down for her.
いやいやいや！
No, no, no!
綿キャンディとフワモコ！
Cotton candy and FuwaMoco!
あ、奥が良くなかった。流しますね！
Ah, the deep part was off. Sending it down!
はい！お願いします！
Okay! Go ahead!
ビブー上手い！
Biboo, you're good!
So small! / ビブー！
So small! / Biboo!
ホッ！ナイス！
Ha! Nice!
オッケー！
Okay!
また来ますよー！
Here comes another one!
みおちゃん、どうですか？
Mio-chan, how is it?
うん、美味しいよね！
Yeah, it's delicious, right?
流しそうめん美味！
Flowing soumen is delicious!
流しそうめん良いよね！
Flowing soumen is great, isn't it?
I'm creating now!
神コンセプト！これちょっと失敗になってきた。
God concept! This one is starting to fail a bit.
これが失敗になってきた！
This is turning into a failure!
大丈夫だよ！今からね、大丈夫だよ！
It's okay! From now on, it'll be fine!
あれ？
Huh?
今日ね、マジでハコスね...
Today, honestly, Hakos...
作ってくれたから、いっぱい食べなきゃ！
...made so much for us, so we gotta eat a lot!
Okay, which one do you want?
チート台があるのかと思うと、ちょっと...
Thinking there might be a cheat station makes me feel...
あと、いっぱいみんなに来てくれることを願うやん！
And we hope a lot of people come by!
ね、みんな食べるために！
Right, for everyone to eat!
みんな、いっぱい食べて！
Everyone, eat lots!
ホッ！取れるかな？
Ha! Can I catch it?
これ、量が多くない？
Isn't this a huge amount?
持って、左...
Hold it, to the left...
With Lunar... / いっぱいあるから...
With Lunar... / Because there's a lot...
大丈夫かもね。
It might be fine.
え、でもさ、このレックウザ、今回はみおちゃんに行くんでしょ？
But wait, this Rayquaza goes to Mio-chan this time, right?
この棒の音が好き。うち車で来たから...
I like the sound of this stick. We came by car, so...
キャー！
Eek!
今回はね、飼い主のみおちゃんのところにレックウザも帰るみたいです。
Looks like this time Rayquaza is going back to its owner, Mio-chan.
フブさんちょっと心配してたよね。このレックウザが無事...
Fubu-san was a bit worried, right? Hoping this Rayquaza...
誰か持って帰ってください、ってね。
...would be safely taken home by someone.
あ、でも...
Ah, but...
あ、いいやん！後でね！
Ah, nice! Later then!
後でね！そうめん美味い！
Later then! Soumen is delicious!
Wait, why do I have them?
Mizuame? Mizuame? / あ、そっちね！
Starch syrup? Starch syrup? / Ah, over there!
やっと... あれ？フブちゃんが作ってる！
Finally... Huh? Fubu-chan is making it!
キャー！マジで？！
Eek! Seriously?!
すごい！ありがとうございます！
Amazing! Thank you very much!
やっとのことで... なんか...
After all that... somehow...
...I think... / え？
...I think... / Eh?
I think I'm losing...
出来上がってきた、これ！
It's coming together, this one!
大変なことになってきた、これ！
This is turning into a mess!
外れちゃってさ... オッケー、オッケー！
It came off... Okay, okay!
なんか... なんかフブちゃん圧縮！
Somehow... Fubu-chan compressed it!
すごい、スター...
Wow, star...
キャー！可愛い！
Eek! So cute!
一層...
Even more...
でも美味いんですよ。それ、みおちゃんにあげないの？
But it's delicious. Aren't you giving that to Mio-chan?
Eh? / 欲しい！
Eh? / I want it!
That's a microphone!
え？これ？！
Eh? This?!
これちがうよ！
This isn't it!
喜んでくれるかな？
I wonder if she'll be happy?
I won!
なんか止まってる
It's stuck!
I won! I win!
みなさん、これでございます
Everyone, here it is!
ルーちゃんの綿あめ...
Lu-chan's cotton candy...
ルーちゃん固まってる
Lu-chan's is hardening.
上の部分はまだいいんだけどさ
The top part is still okay, but...
これどうなったと思う？
What do you think happened to this?
That's okay, people!
雪みたいだね
It looks like snow!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
取れない！
I can't get it off!
頑張って！
Do your best!
ネリッサがハンバーガー...
Nerissa is holding a burger...
なんで？
Why?
これパテだよ！
This is a patty!
パテだ、これ！
It's a patty, this!
なんや、でっか！
What, it's huge!
強そう！
It looks strong!
見せて
Show me!
強そう！
It looks strong!
オッケー、行け！Let's go!
Okay, go! Let's go!
ちょっと色...
A bit of color...
なんやこれ！
What is this!
乾杯！
Cheers!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
持って帰って...
Take it home...
食べたいよ
I want to eat it.
え、フワモコさ、なんか夏祭りの思い出とかある？
Eh, FuwaMoco, do you have any summer festival memories?
ないです！
We don't!
1個だけ！引っ越してからは行ってない...
Just one! We haven't gone since we moved...
あ、そうなんだ！
Oh, really!
夏祭りは1回しか行ってなくて
We've only gone to a summer festival once.
りんご飴と、キャンディ！
Candy apple and candy!
お願いします、先輩！
Please, Senpai!
人形すくいやばい
Doll scooping is crazy.
モコタがやってるときにちょっと勢いが強すぎて...
When Mocota was doing it, she was a bit too aggressive...
金魚すくいが丘の上にあって...
The goldfish scooping was at the top of a hill...
モコタ結構勢いよく...
And Mocota was pretty energetic...
ぼーっとしてたら、金魚が...
While spacing out, the goldfish...
足の裏、靴下についたのが気づかなくて...
didn't notice it got stuck to the bottom of her sock...
体重を偶然にその靴下に、この足に...
And put her weight accidentally onto that sock, onto this foot...
で、プチッて...
And squish...
ねえ、やめてそれ！
Hey, stop that!
歩いてたら...
While walking...
踏まれて、その丘にコロコロコロ...
it got stepped on and rolled down the hill...
そしたらその金魚が...
And then that goldfish...
ねえ、なんでそんな怖いこと言うの！
Hey, why are you telling such a scary story!
怖すぎる！
It's way too scary!
金魚の思い出じゃないよ！
That's not a fond goldfish memory!
これからカットしていきます
Now we're going to cut it.
やばい、それ！
That's awful!
ビブー、なんか思い出ある？夏祭りの
Biboo, do you have any memories of summer festivals?
I remember the summer festival!
あ、花火！
Ah, fireworks!
花火！Fire... なんだっけ？
Fireworks! Fire... what was it?
花火はいったよ！花火怖くて...
We went to see fireworks! Fireworks were scary...
なんで？Why? Why scary?
Why? Why scary?
Oh, big!
あ、ビッグ！
Ah, big!
ちょっとバンバンやめて！
Stop making bang sounds!
ねえ、今さ、今ビブーが話してんのにさ...
Hey, right now while Biboo is speaking...
マジ、もうバンバンバンってフワモコが...
Seriously, FuwaMoco is just going bang bang bang...
フワモコやめなさい！暴れるのは！
FuwaMoco, stop wilding out!
ビブー勝つ！あ、勝ったね！
Biboo wins! Ah, she won!
これ取れて... ビブー！ビブー！
She got this... Biboo! Biboo!
ビブーが話してんのにビブーが取ってくれたヨーヨーでこうバンバンやってんのやばいだろ、ビブーに向かって！
Doing bang bang at Biboo with the yo-yo she got for you while she's talking is crazy!
ちなみにネリッサは夏祭りの...
By the way, Nerissa, any summer festival memories?
Yummy yummy! うれしい！
Yummy yummy! I'm happy!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
すいません、これ壊しました！
Sorry, we broke this!
フワモコが壊しました、これ！強すぎた！
FuwaMoco broke this! It was too strong!
フワモコやばいだろ！
FuwaMoco is insane!
別の黄色のヨーヨーダメだったね
The other yellow yo-yo didn't work, right?
ヨーヨーダメだったからやめて、ヨーヨーダメだったね
The yo-yo didn't work so stop, the yo-yo didn't work.
ヨーヨーのせいだ！
It's the yo-yo's fault!
ヨーヨーのせいじゃねえよ！
It's NOT the yo-yo's fault!
これさ、ミオちゃんが1個1個作ったの！
Mio-chan made these one by one!
みお先輩、ありがとうございます！
Mio-senpai, thank you very much!
やったー！
Yay!
え、もう1個？もう1個いいよ！
Eh, another one? Another one is fine!
取ってくれました！新しいのもいいですか？
She got it for us! Is a new one okay too?
いいよ、いいよ！
Sure, go ahead!
You make me go again? You can take any one!
Nice!
あ、本当だ
Oh, you're right.
え、これ、ヨーヨーも見せる？
Wait, should I show the yo-yos too?
グレープソーダ
Grape soda.
おー！
Oh!
たぶん...
Probably...
あ、ケチャップだ！
Ah, it's ketchup!
ワイン！
Wine!
No, that one, that one. Which one?
Which one? Oh my god.
飴、えっと、どうやって作るんですか？
How do you make the cotton candy?
え、まず好きな色を選んで...
First, pick your favorite color...
So pretty! すごく綺麗！
So pretty!
何色にする？
What color do you want?
今まで何色...もうちょっと優しくするね。
What colors so far... I'll go easier on you.
えー、でもオレンジ...オレンジとか作った？みおちゃん。
Eh, but orange... Did we make orange yet, Mio-chan?
はーい！
Yes!
みおちゃん、今日まだ出てない色ある？
Mio-chan, are there any colors we haven't used today?
オレンジまだかも。
Maybe orange isn't used yet.
オレンジまだだって！
She says orange hasn't been used!
じゃあオレンジにしよっか。
Then let's make orange.
じゃあオレンジ、あー、このカップに入れてください。
Then please put orange into this cup.
はい！
Okay!
ハイ、ノー、ハイ！
High, low, high!
あら、夢見がちね。
My, aren't you a dreamer?
この辺オレンジつけるだろ。つけるだろ。
Putting orange around here, right? Right?
はい、これで一杯ね、やってください。
Okay, use one full cup of this.
うい。
Yep.
大丈夫？
Is it alright?
で、この真ん中に入れて...
And put it right in the middle...
そう！
That's it!
You making that? How's it going?
It's going okay.
これ入れてスイッチオンしてしばし待つ。
Put it in, turn on the switch, and wait a bit.
Yeah, which one?
あん！
Ah!
お！え？完成？
Oh! Huh? Finished?
えーっと、これを...
Um, this...
ピザ！
Pizza!
ねぇ、コメントで「ヨーヨーで暴れてるの誰？」って言われてるよ。
Hey, comments are asking "Who's going wild with the yo-yo?"
誰ですか？ヨーヨーで暴れてるの。
Who is going wild with the yo-yo?
ボコちゃん！
Moko-chan!
I'll make it together!
ヨーヨーで遊んでんの。
Playing with the yo-yo.
それてくるくるくるーってしたら垂れて...
And if you spin it round and round, then...
もうちょっとね、もうちょっとね。
A little bit more, a little bit more.
ここにあのコットンキャンディーティーチャー...
Here, our cotton candy teacher...
コットンキャンディーティーチャー・みぶさんがいますから。
Cotton candy teacher Mibu-san is here.
みぶさんは今バーガーを...
Mibu-san is currently doing burgers...
はい、代わります。
Okay, taking over.
いいよ、みぶさん。
Go ahead, Mibu-san.
I don't have Hasami...
We have Hasami.
ずっと棒を挿す...あ、待つしかねぇんだ！
Keep inserting the stick... Ah, we just have to wait!
待つしかないんだよ。
We just have to wait.
え、ハコスさん、夏の思い出ある？
Eh, Hakos-san, do you have any summer memories?
夏の思い出？夏祭り、夏祭り！
Summer memories? Summer festival, summer festival!
祭りの思い出ないっしょ？だって本当の祭りは...
No memories of festivals, right? Because real festivals...
行ったことないんじゃ...
You haven't been to one...
そうだ、言ってたわ！
Oh right, she did say that!
ないよ！
None!
食べたい！
I want to eat!
ちょっと待って、モコちゃん...
Wait a second, Moko-chan...
モコちゃん、あのさ、ヨーヨーで暴れるのやめてずっとさ...
Moko-chan, stop going wild with the yo-yo...
暴れてない！
I'm not going wild!
モコちゃん、これしてこれして！
Moko-chan, do this, do this!
大丈夫？本当に。
Are you really okay?
You haven't eaten? No, of course I will.
あーいいね！
Oh, nice!
Yeah, people already gave up.
これはみおちゃんのお手本...
This is Mio-chan's sample...
Look how I'm doing it.
I don't know how this happened.
Somehow I'm not surprised.
あ、出た出た！
Ah, it came out!
No, no, I wanted to make a burger.
Yes, I'm... I love burgers.
みおちゃん、どうですか？夏祭りは。
Mio-chan, how is the summer festival?
Is it working?
なんか出てきた！
Something came out!
ぐるぐる！
Round and round!
くるくるー！
Twirling around!
あんばれ、ぐるぐる！
Hang in there, round and round!
I need water, right?
これめっちゃムズいよ、マジで。
This is really hard, seriously.
今のところみぶしか成功してない。
So far, only Mibu succeeded.
Pick up from...
がつてむずい！
It's super hard!
経験者ですよ、私。
I'm experienced at this.
お仕事で子供のために作った。
I made it for kids at work.
え、モコちゃん、綿あめ上手いの？
Eh, Moko-chan, are you good at making cotton candy?
そうそう！
Yeah, yeah!
へぇー！
Wow!
とりあえずティッシュペーパーに...
For now, on the tissue paper...
Nice, nice!
ナイス、ナイス！
なんでもいいんだって！
Anything works!
Maybe you start with the kitty?
You just make what makes you happy.
Don't leave me!
追いついてきたの遅いぞ！
You're slow catching up!
Look at the ball, that makes sense.
うわー！
Woah!
ちょっと近すぎた、すいません！
Got a bit too close, sorry!
やめてー、壊れる！
Stop it, it's gonna break!
すいません！
Sorry!
うまい、モコちゃん！
You're good, Moko-chan!
うま！
So good!
出来ましたー！
All done!
すごい、やい！
Amazing, yay!
モコちゃん、コツは？
Moko-chan, what's the trick?
How's it open?
棒を濡らさない...
Don't wet the stick...
そんな事言わないでよ、モコちゃん。
Don't say that, Moko-chan.
棒を濡らさないとかさ...
Like "don't wet the stick"...
流しそうめん食べたい！
I want to eat nagashi somen!
流しそうめんね。
Nagashi somen, right.
レッツ流しそうめんにしよう！
Let's do nagashi somen!
お腹空いたー！
I'm hungry!
No, no, no, we have to do the nagashi somen.
流しそうめんやりたい！
I wanna do nagashi somen!
これ、上から流すからね。
I'll pour it from the top, okay?
すげー！
Awesome!
怖いです！
I'm scared!
信用できない！
I can't trust this!
べーちゃん...
Bae-chan...
べーは上手いんだよね、こういうの
Bae's really good at these kinds of things, huh?
あ、行った！すごい！
Ah, it went down! Awesome!
あ、行った行った！ほい！
Ah, there it goes, there it goes! Here!
うわああ！
Whoa!
すごい！できた！
Amazing! She got it!
先輩たちにもさ...
Offer some to the seniors too...
ほら！すんごい...
Look! It's so cool...
ここにおいて... そうめん美味っ！
Put it here... The somen is so good!
パン！あ、落とした
Bang! Ah, I dropped it.
これ流すんだよ
You flow this down!
吸うの苦手すぎるだろ
You're way too bad at slurping them up!
あ、はじめ来た！
Ah, Hajime's here!
じゃんじゃーん！
Ta-da!
わあ、すごい！
Wow, awesome!
よし！ナイス！
All right! Nice!
ナイス！
Nice!
みおちゃん、これ流してあげて
Mio-chan, flow this for her.
おー、すごい！
Oh, amazing!
ナイス！
Nice!
すごーい！流してきた！
Awesome! It's flowing!
そうめん！
Somen!
ゴー！
Go!
さっきまで飛んでたんだよ
It was flying around until just now!
ハーイ！
Yay!
キャッチ！イエス、キャッチ！
Catch! Yes, catch!
はい、そうめん！
Here, somen!
そうめん！
Somen!
ナイスキャッチ！
Nice catch!
Do you want it? Okay, put it!
Here you go!
はい、そうめん！
Here comes the somen!
そうめん！
Somen!
美味い！
Delicious!
美味しそうね、これやめて
Looks tasty... Stop that.
やばい、ハンバーグ作ってる
Oh no, she's making a hamburger patty!
ハンバーグ作ってる！
She's making a hamburger patty!
Moco-chan, this is for you!
食べてないけど
She hasn't eaten it yet though.
あの、ヨーヨーやって、はじめ
Hey Hajime, try the yo-yo!
待って、お腹いっぱい
Wait, I'm full!
いっぱい？一旦ストップね
Full? Let's stop for a moment.
That smells like ketchup.
You're making the hamburger, man!
How many?
Oh my! 美味しそうでいい
Oh my! It looks delicious and good!
何にもしてない
I haven't done anything.
はじめ、頑張れ！
Hajime, do your best!
どう？ うん、美味しい！
How is it? Mm, delicious!
良かった！すごーい！
Glad to hear! Awesome!
はじめはいまね...
Hajime is currently...
やってみよう！
Let me try!
Let's try!
モサモサしたやつが光るやつ
The fluffy one is the one that glows.
もっちゃ、もっちゃ
Moccha, Moccha.
おお！すごい！
Oh! Amazing!
うわー！
Whoa!
ナイス！取れてる！
Nice! You caught it!
はじめ来た！
Hajime got one!
ヤッホー！
Yahoo!
取れた！ナイス！
I got it! Nice!
景品！え、これ何ですか？
A prize! Eh, what is this?
いいよ、持って帰って
It's okay, take it home with you.
サンキュー！
Thank you!
ねぇねぇねぇ！お前、マスターになってる
Hey hey hey! You've become a master at this!
取れた！美味しかった！
I got it! That was delicious!
すごい！
Awesome!
そうめん、ようこそ！
Welcome to the somen!
えー、そうなんだ！流してー！
Eh, is that so? Flow it down!
I'm determined now, I have to finish.
ねぇ、死ぬほどこれあるから
Hey, we have a ton of these.
流しそうめんください！
Flowing somen, please!
あ、ハンバーガー？
Ah, a hamburger?
おー！めっちゃ作れてる！
Oh! You made so many!
すごい！出来が良い！
Awesome! They turned out so good!
めっちゃ可愛い！
So cute!
いいね！
Nice!
私はアメリカ人です。バーガーが好きです。
I am American. I like burgers.
何にも来ない... あ、そうなんだ
Nothing is coming... Ah, is that so?
ねねち、あとでわたあめ作ってよ！
Nene-chi, make cotton candy for me later!
はい、いいよ！作ってあげる！
Sure, okay! I'll make it for you!
I'm trying.
I don't think we have tape.
あ、作る？ はい！
Ah, you're making it? Yes!
どうぞ！はい、流します！
Go ahead! Okay, I'm flowing it!
来い来い来い！
Come, come, come!
元気すぎるだろ
You're way too energetic!
やったー！タダメシだー！
Yay! Free food!
タダメシ！
Free food!
めっちゃ腹減ってる！グミ作りたい！
I'm super hungry! I wanna make gummies!
グミ？オッケー！
Gummies? Okay!
よし
Alright!
ドーナツ作ってください
Please make a donut!
すごい！すごい！
Awesome! Awesome!
ドルフィン？
A dolphin?
めちゃくちゃうまい！
It's so good!
温かくなったら出てくるから、お腹
It'll come out when it warms up inside.
よし、グラグラしてる
Alright, it's shaking!
暖かくなるまで時間がかかる
It takes time to warm up.
アイス屋さんもある！
There's an ice cream shop too!
ちなみに一番上手いのはビブス
By the way, Biboo is the best at this.
え、こっちは？
Eh, what about over here?
逃げてしまった
It ran away.
どっちがいいですか？アイスかグミか
Which one would you like? Ice cream or gummy?
グミ！作った方がいい
Gummy! It's better to make it!
いっちゃん、全部いっちゃう！
All of it is going in!
あ、入ってきた！
Ah, here it comes!
選んでください
Please choose.
アイスかグミか
Ice cream or gummy?
たくさん、たくさん！
Lots and lots!
うまいや！めっちゃうまい！
So good! You're really good!
あ、白！白なんです
Ah, white! It's white.
テープが...
The tape...
いいです、オッケー
It's fine, okay.
あー！飛び出してきた！
Ah! It flew out!
これ、これ、あめ
This, this, candy.
待って、もう一回ください
Wait, please do it one more time.
待って！キャンディ
Wait! Candy.
どっちがいいですか？アイスかグミか
Which one do you want? Ice cream or gummy?
来い、来い、来い！
Come on, come on, come on!
あ、言えた！うわー！
Ah, you said it! Woah!
今、待って
Wait right now.
ネリッサ、カワイイじゃなくて、アイスかグミか
Nerissa, not 'cute', ice cream or gummy?
教えて！キャンディ
Tell me! Candy.
キャンディ？キャンディちょうだい
Candy? Give me candy.
はい、はい、はい！
Yes, yes, yes!
なんかね、いくつになってもね...
You know, no matter how old you get...
いくつになってもね、アイスってね...
No matter how old you get, ice cream...
あ、来る来る来る！
Ah, here it comes!
来る来る！うわー！
Here it comes! Woah!
あ、詰まった！あ、出た！
Ah, it got stuck! Ah, it came out!
これダメ！クルクルクル...
This is no good! Spinning around...
クルクルクル...
Spinning around...
いや！嫌だ！
No! No way!
いやいやいや...
No, no, no...
嫌だ！嫌だ！
No! No!
綿あめと何かが...
Cotton candy and something else...
嫌だ、嫌だ、嫌だ！
No, no, no!
綿あめ会場盛り上がりすぎだろ
The cotton candy venue is getting way too hyped.
ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って！
Wait a sec, wait a sec!
ヤバいよ、ヤバいよ！
This is bad, this is bad!
ヤバい、ヤバい！
This is bad, bad!
ハジメ頑張れ！頑張れ！
Hajime, do your best! Do your best!
手を躍らせるんだ！
Make your hands dance!
あ、いらっしゃいませ
Ah, welcome!
速くなっちゃった、綿あめ
It got fast, the cotton candy.
ゆっくり...
Slowly...
もうちょっとゆっくり...
A little slower...
あー！
Ah!
助けて！上！
Help me! Up!
あ、今...ちょっと待って...
Ah, now... wait a moment...
あー！
Ah!
追わないで！スバルが持ってきたやつだから
Don't chase it! That's the one Subaru brought!
えっと、えっと...
Um, um...
あー！
Ah!
飛んでっちゃった！
It flew away!
助けて！助けて！
Help me! Help me!
どうしたらいいのこれ？笑ってないで！
What should I do with this? Stop laughing!
ねねが壊す、やめろ
Nene is gonna break it, stop.
助けて！
Help me!
うわー！
Woah!
すごーい！
Amazing!
あははは！
Hahaha!
やったー！
Hooray!
ビブスの手に付いた！ネリッサ！
It stuck to Biboo's hand! Nerissa!
あー！
Ah!
注文お願い！注文お願いします！
Order please! Order please!
完成品！
Finished product!
バーガー＆ポテト
Burger & fries.
コーラつき！コーラつき！
With Cola! With Cola!
ネリッサが作ったね、スーパーティーだし
Nerissa made it, and it's Super Tea.
うわー！
Woah!
そしてハジメの作った...
And the one Hajime made...
やったー！お茶あめです
Yay! It's tea candy.
いただきます
Bon appétit.
これ、ビブ...
This, Bib...
食べてみてください
Please try eating it.
いただきます、硬くて...
Bon appétit, it's hard...
粘土みたいになるんだ、綿あめが...
It becomes like clay, the cotton candy...
えー、そうだんだ！
Eh, really?!
噛めないでしょ
You can't chew it, right?
何ポイント？
How many points?
100 points! Nice, nice!
MAX 100 points?
何ポイントこれ？
How many points is this?
すごい！マジ？
Amazing! Really?
10 points!
優しい！
So kind!
買い出し行って参る！
I'm off to buy supplies!
わたあめ欲しいな
I want cotton candy.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
食べつくす！
Devour it all!
あ！なんか煙出てる！
Ah! Smoke is coming out!
今オフになってるけど...
It's turned off right now, but...
わたあめ屋、一回飛びます！
Cotton candy shop is temporarily taking a break!
ごめんね一回...
Sorry, just for a moment...
ヤバい！ねねち、ハジメがわたあめ機壊した！
Oh no! Nenechi, Hajime broke the cotton candy machine!
ごめんなさい！
I'm so sorry!
ヤバい！煙がヤバい！
Oh no! The smoke is crazy!
見ちゃったよ...
I saw it...
それ危ないんで... メンテナンス中だね、これ。
That's dangerous... It's under maintenance now.
メンテナンス...
Maintenance...
あ、ボタン押すと必ず煙出てる...
Ah, whenever you press the button, smoke comes out...
じゃあ大丈夫か。もうちょっとで出来る。
Then is it fine? It'll be ready soon.
美味しい！
Delicious!
めでたい！
Congratulations!
あ、それオンになってる！
Ah, that's turned ON!
お掃除...
Cleaning...
じゃあわたあめ屋さん、ちょっと一回休止です。
Okay, so the cotton candy shop is temporarily closed.
メンテナンスが入ります！
Maintenance in progress!
ごちそうさでした！
Thank you for the treat!
美味しかった！
It was delicious!
うわー！
Woah!
リアル...
So realistic...
Is that yakisoba, yum?
Oh, no...
Gummy candy?
Oh, why? I'm scared.
You gave that one time!
That was for my life! It's yummy!
最後！最後！
Last one! Last one!
おい！
Hey!
ヤバい！来い！
Oh no! Come on!
ねねち行ける？
Can you get it, Nenechi?
行けないかも... 頑張って！
Maybe I can't... Do your best!
フミ頑張れ！行けないかも...
Fumi, do your best! Maybe I can't...
ちなみにみおちゃんとビブーは成功してる。
By the way, Mio-chan and Bijou succeeded.
なんで？！どうやって？！
Why?! How?!
聞いたらね、「えぇっ？」てなるよ。
If you hear how, you'll go "Ehh?!"
If you're gonna feed it to someone else...
頑張れ、ねねち！
Do your best, Nenechi!
実力で取ってたよ、ちゃんと。2個取り！
They got it with pure skill properly. Two at once!
あー！
Ahhh!
やっぱり欲張ると良くないね。
As expected, being greedy isn't good.
もう一回いいよ。
You can try one more time.
これちなみにみおちゃんが全部手作りしてるから。
By the way, Mio-chan made all of these by hand.
すごい！
Amazing!
やっぱりドーンと入れるわけじゃないですよ。
You're not supposed to just slam it in.
はい！そうめん屋へいらっしゃい、いらっしゃい！
Yes! Welcome to the somen shop! Welcome!
えーっと... オッケー、待ちました！
Ummm... Okay, ready!
ーい！流します！
Yayy! Sending it down!
ここを通るの信じて！
Believe it's gonna pass through here!
ナイッショ！ナイッショ！取れた！
Nice shot! Nice shot! Caught it!
もう一回！もう一回おいで！
One more time! Come one more time!
気をつけて！罰ゲームのやつ...
Be careful! That's the punishment game one...
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
勝った勝った勝った！頼んだ！
Won won won! I left it to you!
あー！
Ahhh!
やったー！本当に辛かったよね。
Yay! That was really spicy, right?
Okay, yeah. I don't want pizza.
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
バンってやると...
If you slam it...
あ、ホントだ！
Ah, it's true!
猫が喜びそう！
Cats would love this!
これやめなさい！このバシバシバシバシやめなさい！
Stop doing that! Stop doing that aggressive slapping!
またバシバシしてる！
Slapping it again!
イエーイ！
Yay!
共鳴、共鳴！
Resonance, resonance!
お！燃えたお！
Oh! It lit up!
イエーイ！
Yaaaaay!
綺麗！
So pretty!
流しちゃってる... あーららら
It's washing away... Ah la la
大丈夫、大丈夫。ねーさま可愛い。
It's okay, it's okay. Sister is so cute.
え、そこからね、回収されてまたね、そうめんになる。
Eh, from there it gets collected and becomes somen again.
変なギミック！
What a weird gimmick!
無限にそうめんだよ！無限そうめん！
It's infinite somen! Infinite somen!
はーい！いらっしゃいー！
Yes! Welcome!
お客さま！
Customer!
ちゃんとね、マナーがありますからね。
There are proper manners, after all.
お客さまー！
Customer~!
お客さま大丈夫ですかー？気をつけてね！
Customer, are you alright~? Be careful!
こっからね、こうやって...
From here, like this...
これ壊さないでね！壊さないでハジメ！
Don't break this! Don't break it, Hajime!
流します！
Sending it down!
頑張れー！
Hang in there!
おっ、やった！
Oh, nice!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
全然大丈夫！
It's completely fine!
Push it with people...
My hand's tickling in it.
I like your fingers.
Your fingers in my mouth... Great.
流しそうめん、超小さいからね。
The nagashi somen is super small, after all.
チーズの匂いがする。
It smells like cheese.
そうめん！
Somen!
痛いの？
Does it hurt?
なんかキャンディだけどチーズの匂い。
It's like candy, but it smells like cheese.
本当だー！
It really does!
スバルの食べないからね。
Subaru won't eat it, you know.
みこちゃんが食べてくれる？
Will Miko-chan eat it for us?
Eat it, sweetie!
You got it, you did it!
変えて変えて！なんかマジやばい。
Switch it, switch it! This is really bad.
ちょっと無くした？
Wait, did you lose it?
初めてのヨーヨー無くしたの？
Did you lose your first yo-yo?
ヨーヨーが無くなったとか...
She says she lost her yo-yo...
流しそうめん...
Nagashi somen...
先輩、もう一回お願い...
Senpai, please do it one more time...
ヨーヨー消えたんで、後でもう一回やってください。
The yo-yo disappeared, so please try again later.
一緒にやりたいな！
I want to do it together!
Yucky, yucky!
またネジが壊れた！
The screw broke again!
もう一回、もう一回！
One more time, one more time!
え、この紐フブキ先輩の？
Huh, is this string Fubuki-senpai's?
あー！行けたー！
Ah! It worked!
行けた、行けた！ありがとうございます！
It worked, it worked! Thank you so much!
You're very welcome! Wanna make it for other people?
フブちゃんもやってみたい！
Fubu-chan wants to try it too!
Here's the pizza!
わんこそば！
Wanko soba!
どんどん言ったらいいんじゃない？
Wouldn't it be better to just keep putting them in?
そうめん流してー！
Send down the somen!
It was dirty! Oh, you want it?
回転させよう！
Let's make it spin!
Open wide!
I'll play with my toys.
渡してどうかな？
How about handing it over?
あるある！じゃあ行こうか。
There is! Then shall we go?
You can do it!
ちょっと難しい...
It's a bit difficult...
優しくね！
Gently!
失敗するわけないんだから！
There's no way we'll fail!
取れたー！
I got it!
セーフ！
Safe!
やったー！
Yay!
Oh, so wet!
リプニの匂いがする。
It smells like Lipovitan.
遊びてぇよ！
I wanna play!
Yeah, the ketchup!
やばい、やばい！
Oh no, oh no!
いいね！
Nice!
Don't break it!
There's so many steps, look at that!
I can't do this!
Yes, you can! You have to commit!
えー、何？
Eh, what?
雑祭りだからね！
Because it's a chaotic festival!
可愛い！
So cute!
これで自己紹介してー。
Introduce yourself with this.
美味しい！
Delicious!
Use my hand, okay?
取れない！
I can't get it!
I need to do this!
I don't like how it feels!
I need to cut it to pieces!
あ、キレイ！
Ah, pretty!
やったー！
Yay!
そうめんください！
Somen, please!
うわー、でもチーズのがヤバいこれ
Whoa, but the cheese one is crazy!
固まりになっちゃう
It's going to clump up and turn into a blob.
回収して！ちゃんと回収して！
Collect it! Collect it properly!
え、今わたあめ作ってるの誰？
Wait, who's making cotton candy right now?
ちゃんと回収してね！
Collect it properly, okay?
うわ、美味そう！
Whoa, looks delicious!
あ、これ固まるから...
Ah, because this hardens...
当たり前でしょ！
Well of course!
It smells! It smells like bacon!
大丈夫！
It's fine! Don't worry!
I can smell it from here, and I'm like 5 steps away!
I can smell it from here, and I'm 5 steps away!
すごい！すごい！すごい尖ってきた
Amazing! It got super sharp!
バレバレじゃん！
It's so obvious!
進化しすぎでしょ！
It's evolving too much!
Look, you said... but look, it's not getting...
早く入れなきゃ！
Hurry and put it in!
やっぱり焦げてるかもしれない！
It might really be burning!
Verify!
わたあめ焦げついて...
The cotton candy is getting burnt...
流しそうめん屋が...取って食べてくださいね
At the flowing somen stand, please catch and eat it!
お前チーク好きすぎるだろ！
You like cheek blush way too much!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
変な匂いするピザ作る？ -うん、本当だ！
Are you making a weird-smelling pizza? -Yeah, it's true!
でもキャンディだけど凄いリアルな匂い
It's candy, but it smells so realistic!
ベーコンもしっかりとベーコンの...
The bacon really smells like bacon...
これがチーズ？ -そう！これがチーズで...
Is this cheese? -Yes, this is cheese!
焦げ焦げすぎるって！
It's way too burnt!
本当はこれ作りたかった
Actually I wanted to make this one!
欲張りだなあ！
So greedy!
上手いね！流しそうめんの才能あるね
You're so good at this! You have a talent for flowing somen!
またヨーヨーキッズが暴れてる！
The yo-yo kids are going wild again!
上手いね！
You're so good!
手をとめないと！
You've got to keep moving your hands!
器用なんだわ！
She's so skillful!
みこじこれチーク菓子？
Mikoji, is this cheek makeup candy?
はーちゃんが一生懸命言ってたから感想言ってあげて
Ha-chan was trying hard to tell you, so give her your thoughts!
3個目だ！
That's the third one!
4個目！
Fourth one!
タコが来た！
Here comes the octopus!
分かりました
Understood.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
ヨーヨーチップス...
Yo-yo chips...
大暴れです
Going wild!
みこ、ロール！
Miko, roll!
オッケー
Okay.
夏祭りの思い出だし...
Since it's summer festival memories...
キラキラ...
Sparkly...
これ最近じゃん！
Wait, this was recent!
めっちゃ光ってる！
It's glowing so much!
ちょっとたこ焼きの形になってきたかも
It's starting to take the shape of takoyaki!
焼きすぎだろ！
You overcooked it!
あ、溢れてる！たこ焼きが！
Ah, it's overflowing! The takoyaki!
ただツンツンつついてる
Just poking and poking...
何かに気づいた！
They realized something!
リボンに込め... 来ないで！
Put it on the ribbon... Don't come!
もっと欲しくなってる！
It wants more!
何色？何色が...
What color? What color...
何色が良かった？
Which color did you want?
青！青を求めて...
Blue! Seeking blue...
食べたい！
Want to eat it!
おー！
Oh!
盛り上がりすぎだろ！
You guys are way too hyped!
盛り上がりすぎだろ、みんな！
Everyone's getting way too hyped!
ねるねるねる...
Knead, knead, knead...
美味しいです
Delicious.
食べられない...
Can't eat it...
そっちのお祭り...
The festival over there...
青あった！青あった！
Found blue! Found blue!
1、2、3、4、5！
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
あれ、これだけ？お箸もないから...
Huh, is this all? There are no chopsticks either...
貰ってこないと...
Need to go get them...
ありがと
Thanks.
ヤバい！
Oh boy!
片手でみんなヨーヨーさ...
Everyone's holding yo-yos in one hand...
今、ヨーヨーを全員に...
Right now, everyone's getting yo-yos...
感覚狂ってる！
Sense of touch is messed up!
みこちにまた渡せるの...
Passing to Miko-chan again...
最後！最後！
Last one! Last one!
無理だよ！3回目...
No way! Third time...
お願いします！
Please!
どうぞ！
Here you go!
なんで放すんだよ！
Why did you let go?!
そうめん取られてんじゃねえかよ！
Isn't the soumen being taken?!
次そうめんが流れてきたー！
Next, soumen flowed down!
おいしょ！
Heave-ho!
トマトソースの匂いが...
Smells like tomato sauce...
大丈夫だよ
It's okay.
怖い！
Scary!
流れます
Flowing down!
おい、お前ふざけんじゃねえぞ！
Hey, don't mess with me!
そうめんどろぼうだ！
It's a soumen thief!
難しい！難しい！
Difficult! Difficult!
まかないのパン...
Staff meal bread...
ねるねるねるね...
Nerunerunerune...
すげえ！そうめん犯罪だ！
Awesome! It's a soumen crime!
これで...
With this...
流します
Flowing it down.
ミオちゃん、そろそろ食べ物食べるの控えといてね
Mio-chan, control yourself from eating food soon, okay?
はい
Yes.
確かに
Indeed.
巨大イベントが起こるんだから
Because a huge event is happening!
商品持ってきたよ
Brought the prizes!
これとソース...
This and sauce...
何？ないの？
What? Isn't there any?
こっちでも用意してあったけど...
We prepared it here too, but...
こっちの分もあるってことね
So there's some here too.
何？商品？
What? Prizes?
はい
Yes.
いつでも準備は
I'm ready anytime...
本気になってから先の話ね
Only after you get serious, though!
ミオちゃん、売れない！
Mio-chan, I can't sell any!
いつでも準備はできてる
I'm ready anytime!
え！？
Huh!?
これ誰なんだよ！行儀...
Who is this?! Manners...
えにょーちゃん、頑張れ！
Enyo-chan, do your best!
あー！そうね！
Ahhh! I see!
おそらくフレンの勝ち！
It's probably Furen's win!
うわー！
Uwah!
５フィンガー！
Five Finger!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
イエーイ！オールゲット！
Yeah! All get!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
素晴らしいものだ
It's a wonderful thing.
はい、全員素晴らしい
Yes, everyone is wonderful.
いやいやいや
No, no, no...
お、毎度コメントありがとうございます
Oh, thank you for the comments as always!
うわー！
Uwah!
うわー！誰だ！？
Uwah! Who is it?!
ここにきて...
Coming here...
お！みんないる！ヤッホー！
Oh! Everyone's here! Yahho!
食べてみて！
Try eating it!
はい、いただきます！
Yes, thank you for the food!
あ、刺身も...
Ah, the sashimi too...
ちょっとね、トラブルがあって
Wait, there was a bit of trouble...
ガチでトラブル...
Seriously, trouble...
見ないで！私のおいしい...
Don't look! My delicious...
美味しい！なんかぶどう味でパチパチしてて...
Delicious! It tastes like grape and is popping...
すごい美味しい！
So delicious!
アイスみたい！
Like ice cream!
すごい美味しいよ、こっちも食べてみて！
It's super tasty, try this too!
めっちゃ可愛い！
So cute!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
はい！ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたん！
Yes! Hololive 5th Gen, Shishiro Botan!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
なんかこれ、ベタベタしてる...
Wait, this is kinda sticky...
ちょっと待って、それは...
Wait a second, that's...
大暴れした初めの...
The crazy start...
ねぇ、美味しい！
Hey, it's delicious!
すごい！
Amazing!
これが...
This is...
変顔で...
With a funny face...
笑うな！
Don't laugh!
なんかちょっと困ってるような表情で...
It looks kinda troubled in its expression...
ぶどう！ぶどうちゃん！
Grape! Grape-chan!
グレープ！
Grape!
酸っぱい酸っぱいからちょっと困ってる顔してるね
It's sour, sour, so it looks a bit troubled!
結構今日の難易度高めとなっておりまして...
The difficulty today is pretty high...
ヨーヨーは...
The yo-yo is...
チーズもベーコンも...
Cheese and bacon too...
今ミオがファイブフィンガーを...
Mio is doing the Five Finger right now...
すごい！
Amazing!
手先が器用なだけだからめっちゃむずい！
Just because you're nimble, it's super hard!
むずい！
Hard!
で、そのあとの綿あめ機は...
And after that, the cotton candy machine...
さっきハジメがやってたんだけど...
Hajime was doing it earlier...
石みたいなの作ってました
making something like a rock.
石！？
A rock?!
で、流しそうめんもこれある
And there's this nagashi somen too.
え、ウザ！
Eh, annoying!
そうなんです！
That's right!
いらっしゃい、いらっしゃい！
Welcome, welcome!
なっちゃん、これ...
Nacchan, this...
これもね...
This too...
なっちゃんのこれを...
Nacchan's this...
じゃあ、先にあれだね
Then first, that, right?
こよ、こよさ...
Koyo, Koyosa...
ここヨーヨーしてみなよ
Try doing yo-yo here!
めっちゃむずいよ、それ！
That's super hard!
でもファイブフィンガーが...
But Five Finger is...
頑張って！
Good luck!
一応...
Just in case...
なんか食ってる！
They're eating something!
めっちゃ楽しい！
So much fun!
あ、これね！
Ah, this one!
これが丸いやつで...
This is the round one...
やばい、美味しそう！
Wow, looks delicious!
美味しいよ！
It's good!
ナイスー！
Nice!
ピンク、ピンクも！
Pink, pink too!
可愛い！
Cute!
ほら！
Look!
ナイス、ナイス！
Nice, nice!
引っかかってる、引っかかってる！
It's caught, it's caught!
あ！あ！
Ah! Ah!
行ける！行ける！
You can do it! You can do it!
キャー！
Kyaa!
１個ゲットだ！
Got one!
あ、回して...
Ah, spinning...
回してない...
Not spinning...
えー！
Ehh?!
パスタみたい！
Like pasta!
パスタみたいね！
It is like pasta!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
うわー！
Uwah!
嬉しい！
So happy!
そう、ここに行ったら...
Yeah, if you go here...
お風呂...
Bath...
股に引っかけて...
Hooking it between legs...
これと、あと普通のヨーヨー
This, and then regular yo-yo
水色！水色がいい！
Light blue! I want light blue!
水色ね！
Light blue, right!
印象的ですね
Impressive, isn't it?
水大量に入れて...
Putting in lots of water...
あ！
Ah!
大丈夫！
It's okay!
キター！
It's here!
１個ゲット！
Got one!
ナイスー！
Nice!
ええー！
Ehhh?!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
うわー！
Uwah!
すごいな！
Amazing!
３個...
Three...
あめ！あめ！
Candy! Candy!
そうそうそう！
Yes yes yes!
そう、そう！
Yes, yes!
髪についちゃった...
It got on my hair...
りんごあめの蜜が髪についちゃった
The apple candy syrup got on my hair...
大変！
Oh no!
待って、待って、待って！
Wait, wait, wait!
先輩、取ってくれました！
Senpai got it off for me!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい！そうめんの準備オッケーです！
Alright! The somen prep is done!
はい！これどうしたらいいの？
Okay! What should I do with this?
ガチな流しそうめん取りに来るから気をつけて
I'm coming to grab some serious flowing somen, so watch out!
え、横取りされる？
Wait, are you gonna steal it from the side?
リリカです、こんにちは！
I'm Ririka! Hello!
いきます！
Here I go!
譲らず...いやダメ！えっ待って！じゃあここ！
No yielding... Wait, no! Hold on! Then right here!
リリカ！お前柵を超えるな！
Ririka! Don't cross the fence!
まずいまずい！リリカ、柵を超えるな！
Uh oh! Ririka, don't cross the fence!
だって取れないんだもん！じゃあここ！
Because I can't reach it! Then over here!
ピカチュウより前に走るのバッドマナーだからね！
Running ahead of Pikachu is bad manners, you know!
そうめんバッドマナーだよ、それ
That's somen bad manners right there.
はい、行くよ！
Alright, here it goes!
流れてない！
It's not flowing!
つぶいるもん！
It's getting clogged!
水がちょっとローです...
The water flow is a bit low...
ぺこさんも早すぎだよ！
Peko-san, you're being too fast too!
いきます！
Here comes more!
いらっしゃい！
Welcome!
リリカは何であんな戦ってたの？
Why was Ririka fighting like that?
狙われてた...
I was being targeted...
大葉を入れました！
I added shiso leaves!
大葉がいっちゃん美味いから！
Shiso is the absolute tastiest!
1位のあずきさんが取りたいんじゃない？
Doesn't 1st place AZKi want to grab it?
絶対その下手(しもて)にいた方が...
You'd definitely be better off downstream...
危ないよ！良くないよこれが！
Dangerous! This isn't good!
前傾姿勢にならないでください！
Please don't lean forward!
スバルは本当は興奮体質だからね
Subaru gets easily excited, after all.
先輩...ヤッホー！
Senpai... Yoo-hoo!
これ凄い美味しい、これ！
This is super delicious!
面白いでしょ！
It's fun, right?
そうめん大満足！
Totally satisfied with the somen!
ヨーヨーのやり方教えてください！
Please teach me how to do the yo-yo!
オッケー！やるぜ！
Okay! Let me try!
リリカ、こういう細かい作業マジで得意だから！
Ririka is seriously good at detailed work like this!
リリカ読め！
Read it, Ririka!
前傾姿勢禁止！
No leaning forward!
羽交い締めにされてる！
She's being pinned in a full nelson!
こうすればいいのか！
Oh, so I should do it like this!
やったー！上手い！
Yay! Nice one!
プロ？上手いね！
Are you a pro? You're good!
これも狙っちゃおうかな！
Maybe I'll aim for this one too!
前傾姿勢禁止だから！
Leaning forward is forbidden!
ガニ股になってる！
You're going bow-legged!
おー！やったー！
Woah! Yay!
でもちぎれた！
But it snapped!
みこゲット！イエーイ！
Got Miko! Yay!
めっちゃ練ってる！
She's mixing it so much!
本当にでっかくなった！
It really got huge!
で、愛情込めることだった
And putting love into it...
すごーい！ / ナイス！
Amazing! / Nice!
なんか、みこちのなんかネルネルネルね
It's like Mikochi's Nerunerunerune...
ふざけんなよ！
Don't fool around!
比べるとちょっと...
Compared to that, it's a bit...
かわいい！ね！
Cute, right!
ナイス！
Nice!
うちの店閉店するよー
Our shop is closing down~
新しいアトラクション...
A new attraction...
待って、フワモコやってみます！
Wait, FWMC will give it a try!
え、いいな～
Oh, nice~
びっくり...やってみてもいいですか？
Surprised... Can we try it too?
3人分...3人分みたいな
3 portions... looks like 3 portions.
Max 3人分
Max 3 portions.
いただきます！
Let me dig in!
いろは前...言ってたんだよ。なんかワンチャンクッキー焼いてから来るらしいけど間に合うか...
Iroha said earlier that she might bake cookies and come, but will she make it...
すごーい！
Awesome!
え、みんなに見せてあげてよ！
Hey, show everyone!
かわいい！
So cute!
うちの店閉店しちゃったんだけど、ヨーヨー屋さんと綿あめ屋さんは開いてて
Our shop closed down, but the yo-yo shop and cotton candy shop are open.
え！これゴッドのクッキーだ！
Wait! This is God's cookie!
美味しい！
Delicious!
すごく美味しい！
It's really delicious!
ねるねるねるね？
Nerunerunerune?
コンビが美味しい！
The combo is delicious!
はい！イズ・ヤミー！
Yes, it's yummy!
いろはクッキー見せてあげた？
Did you show Iroha's cookies?
食べたーい！
I want to eat it!
フワモコも食べたい！
FWMC wants to eat too!
え、すごーい！
Whoa, awesome!
え、食べてみたーい！
Whoa, I want to try it!
教えて教えて！
Tell us, tell us!
コンビ、コンビしたい！
Combo, I want to do a combo!
じゃあ、これを...失礼します！
Then, this... excuse me!
ねるねるやば！コンビできた！
Neruneru is crazy! A combo!
オッケー、オッケー！
Okay, okay!
ねぇ、嫉妬する！
Hey, I'm jealous!
しっとりクッキー美味しい！
Moist cookies are delicious!
これやばい！ネコちゃんが食ってるみたい！
This is crazy! Looks like a cat is eating it!
Don't drop it!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
黒幕が大変なことやってる！
The mastermind is doing something crazy!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
みんな見て！みこちのねるねるねるねと、えーっと...
Everyone look! Mikochi's Nerunerunerune and, um...
りんご飴！
Apple candy!
の、コンビネーション！
...combination!
いろはクッキー！そして...
Iroha's cookies! And...
え、なんかディップ、ディップしてる！
Wait, she's dipping it!
ござるクッキー！
Gozaru cookies!
やばい、妖怪大戦争みたいになってる！
Oh no, it looks like a Great Yokai War!
自分で作ったアイスできあがった！
The homemade ice cream is ready!
えー、いいなー！
Aww, lucky!
超かわいい！
Super cute!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
超かわいい！
Super cute!
誰のこれ？チェリーもついてる！
Whose is this? It even has cherries!
結構時間かけて作ったんですね、ネリスが！
Nerys spent quite a bit of time making it!
Lots of time and effort into it, right?
愛情込めて！
With lots of love!
じゃあ、ちょっと...そろそろ始めます！
Well then, let's get started soon!
伝説のイベント、みおちゃんが来たらやりたいと思います！
We'll do the legendary event when Mio-chan arrives!
美味しい！
Delicious!
今から何をするかを説明します！
Now I'll explain what we're going to do!
こっちも食べたい！
I want to eat this too!
食べて！
Go ahead and eat!
それでは、夏祭り最後のイベントになります！
And now, it's time for the final summer festival event!
最後のイベントは、ミオちゃんのワンワンレースです！
The final event is Mio-chan's Woof-Woof Race!
ワンワンレース！
Woof-Woof Race!
何をするかと言うと...カメラをオンにします！
As for what we'll be doing... switching on the camera!
おー！
Ooh!
ミオが下になっちゃってる？本当だ！
Is Mio underneath? You're right!
何をするかと言うと、今からミオちゃんが犬のおもちゃと競争します！
What we'll do is, Mio-chan will race against a toy dog!
ええー！
Ehh?!
皆さん見えますか？ワンちゃんが...見えます！
Everyone, can you see? The doggie... yes, we see it!
ワンちゃんはこの赤い線まで走ります！
The doggie will run up to this red line!
おー！
Ooh!
そしてミオちゃんは
And Mio-chan...
ここから300m走ります
...will run 300 meters from here!
誰が一番最初に着くかをみんな予想してください
Everyone, please guess who will reach the finish line first!
当たった人はポイントがある
Whoever guesses right will get points!
えー！同時に走るんじゃないんだ！
Eh?! She's not running at the same time?!
そうなんです
That's right!
難解！
That's tricky!
犬5匹は
The 5 dogs...
もう疲れてる！
...are already tired!
もう大丈夫ね
Are they okay?!
電池が入ってるよね
They have batteries in them, right?
ミオ先輩は電池が入ってないから大丈夫
Mio-senpai doesn't have batteries, so she's fine.
エントリーナンバーワンの犬
Dog Entry Number 1.
エントリーナンバーワン！
Entry Number 1!
あ、違うね！英語で説明してもらった！
Ah, wait! She explained in English!
We have reached the final event of today's Summer Festival.
We have now reached the...
ミオちゃん、走れ！
Mio-chan, run!
ミオちゃん、スカートがめくれてるよ！
Mio-chan, your skirt is flipping up!
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
スカートがめくれてるよ！
Your skirt is flipping up!
The event is "Run, Mio-chan! Run 100 meters!"
So we have...
...dogs on screen, as you can see, that will be racing against Mio-chan.
1 out of 5... if they reach the red line first...
ミオちゃん！スカートが...
Mio-chan! Your skirt...
Mio-senpai has to run 300 meters.
Please place your bets on who you think will win!
If you guess correctly, there will be a prize!
絶対ミオ先輩が勝つ！
Mio-senpai will definitely win!
そりゃそうだろ！
Of course she will!
ちなみにワンちゃんはどんな感じで動くかっていうと
By the way, to show you how these dogs move...
They're dog toys.
The dog toys...
え！速い！速い！
Eh?! So fast! Fast!
ゼンマイでワンワンワンワンって
They wind up and go bark bark bark bark!
きゃー！
Kyaa!
じゃ、エントリーナンバー1、なんかこのすごいふわふわしてる白い犬。
So, Entry Number 1, this super fluffy white dog.
はい。
Yes.
結構速いです。
It's pretty fast.
ちょっと傾いた犬が欲しい！
I want a slightly tilted dog!
「欲しい」やめてほしい。
Please stop saying "I want".
可愛い！
Cute!
エントリーナンバー2、え、ちょっとキャバリアっぽい、なんかコロネっぽいやつ。
Entry Number 2, a kind of Cavalier-like, Korone-like one.
あ、可愛い！
Ah, cute!
みんな帰ろう！
Let's all go home!
え、速い！
Eh, fast!
そしてエントリーナンバー3、イヌッチ！
And Entry Number 3, Inutchi!
イヌッチ！
Inutchi!
みこちのイヌッチ！
Miko-chi's Inutchi!
イヌッチ！がんばれ！
Inutchi! Good luck!
そして、エントリーナンバー4、柴犬！
And Entry Number 4, Shiba Inu!
わ！
Wa!
2号！2号やばい！
No. 2! No. 2 is crazy!
2号やばい！2号やばい！2号やばい！
No. 2 is crazy! No. 2 is crazy! No. 2 is crazy!
2号が速いか。
Is No. 2 fast?
2号速いね。
No. 2 is fast, huh.
ということで、そっ、そっ...
So, that, that...
イヌッチ！
Inutchi!
あの、こっから落っこちたら即アウト！
Um, if they fall off from here, immediate disqualification!
なるほど！
I see!
落っこちたら即アウトで、えー...
If they fall off, immediate disqualification, and...
誰が一番速いでしょうかというレースになります。
...this will be a race to see who is the fastest.
これ、けっこう不平だね？
Isn't this pretty unfair?
え？
Eh?
4番、すぐ...
No. 4 immediately...
4番は曲がるかな？まあ、それも運ということで。
Will No. 4 turn? Well, that's down to luck too.
それじゃあ、ちょっと皆さん予想してください。ちなみにミオちゃん、100mの...
So, please make your predictions. By the way, Mio-chan, what's your 100m...
100m何秒？
...time for 100m?
ちょっと待ってください。
Wait a moment please.
走ってきたんですけど、300mは無理なので150mになりました。
I ran, but 300m was impossible, so it became 150m.
あ、150mね！
Ah, 150m then!
ミオちゃん、150mになったのね。
Mio-chan reduced it to 150m.
半減してる。
It halved.
50mは？
How about 50m?
17秒とか...
Like 17 seconds...
え、そんな掛かります？100m...
Eh, does it take that long? 100m...
100m17秒？
100m in 17 seconds?
え、17？
Eh, 17?
え、そんなもんじゃないですか？
Eh, isn't it around that?
あ、そうなんだ。
Ah, really.
17、18...
17, 18...
あれ？50mが10とか？
Huh? 50m is around 10 seconds?
そうか、50m遅いと10。
Ah right, if slow, 50m is 10.
そうか、小学生で7秒とか...
I see, elementary schoolers do around 7 seconds...
7秒？
7 seconds?
7秒超速い！
7 seconds is super fast!
ちなみにワンワンワンは、えーっとね...
By the way, the dogs are, well...
え、これワンワンのさ、タイム言っていい？
Wait, can I tell you the dogs' times?
はい！
Yes!
ワンワンワン、ゴールまで行くのに、まあ平均30ぐらい。
For the dogs to reach the goal, average is about 30 seconds.
えーー！
Eh---!
まあ速い奴もいるし...
Well, some are fast...
頑張れないかも...
I might not be able to do it...
いや、勝ってるよ！勝ってる！
No, you're winning! Winning!
勝ってる！
You're winning!
お腹いっぱいかな...
Full stomach maybe...
ちなみに、ミオちゃんが今何メートル走ってるっていうのは、フブちゃんが口頭で説明してくれます。
By the way, Fubu-chan will verbally explain how many meters Mio-chan has run.
はい！
Yes!
なるほど。
I see.
150mくらいなんだけど、ここのメーターで...
It's about 150m, but with the meter here...
...あの測っていて、
...we're measuring,
大体うちが30秒くらい走った、
and roughly the distance I ran in 30 seconds,
距離を、あの、測りましたので、
we measured that distance,
その距離をゴール地点としております。
and set that distance as the goal line.
はい！
Okay!
それでは皆さん予想してください！
Now then, everyone please make your predictions!
どの犬が1位なのか！決まったら...
Which dog will take 1st place! Once decided...
はい！
Yes!
ミオ先輩！大神！
Mio-senpai! Ookami!
イヌッチね。
Inutchi, right.
1番のイヌッチに賭けた。
I bet on No. 1 Inutchi.
で、2番。キャバリア。
And No. 2. Cavalier.
じゃあ予想ね。
So your prediction.
ミオ先輩！
Mio-senpai!
ミオ先輩にブッパするっす！
I'm going all in on Mio-senpai!
ミオ先輩！
Mio-senpai!
圧勝のようにミオ先輩が勝つんでしょう。
Mio-senpai will win by a landslide.
本当？！
Really?!
もちろん！
Of course!
大丈夫か？
Are you sure?
みんな決まったら...
Once everyone decides...
じゃ、みこちさんね。
Okay, Miko-chi.
ミオが勝ちそうだけど...
Mio looks like she'll win, but...
2の犬がやりそうだ。
...Dog No. 2 seems like it can do it.
一生懸命走ります！
I'll run with all my might!
ラミィは2番のキャバリア。
Lamy chooses No. 2 Cavalier.
キャバリアね。なんで？
Cavalier, huh? Why?
コロネだから。
Because it's Korone.
コロネだからね。
Because it's Korone, right.
1番のプードル！
No. 1 Poodle!
ちょ、待って。ミオちゃん誰一人いなくても...
Wait, nobody chose Mio-chan...
ミオ社畜だから...
Mio is a company slave...
ちょっとミオ社畜は信用しない、今のところ。
I don't trust Mio the company slave for now.
ひどい！
That's awful!
こよりは？
Koyori, who's your pick?
ミオ先輩！選んで！
Mio-senpai! Pick one!
2番！2番！3番ではない！2番ね！
Number 2! Number 2! Not 3, Number 2! Got it?
まずはミオ先輩に全ぶっぱで！
First, I'm going all in on Mio-senpai!
おー！はじめて！気持ちいい！
Oh, nice! That feels so good!
リリカも！ミオ先輩足つるまで走ってください！
Ririka too! Run until your legs cramp, Mio-senpai!
えっと、ミオ先輩でタイカン...
Um, going with Mio-senpai for Taikan...
おー！フレンも？
Oh! Furen too?
そう、ミオ先輩でしょ！
Yeah, it's gotta be Mio-senpai!
え、ハコスは？
What about Hakos?
いや、ミオ先輩でしょうが！
I mean, obviously Mio-senpai!
りりむは？
What about Ririmu?
まだ言ってない人いる？もう言った全員。
Is there anyone who hasn't voted yet? Everyone voted.
スバル先輩言ってないんじゃないですか？
Didn't Subaru-senpai not vote yet?
4番不人気っすよ、今。
Number 4 is really unpopular right now.
え、じゃあ...じゃあ、4！
Huh? Then... then Number 4!
ちょっと待って、JP誰一人ミオちゃんに入れてないのヤバいだろ！
Wait a second, isn't it crazy that not a single JP member voted for Mio-chan?!
入れてる入れてる！フムちゃんが最初から入れてる！
They did, they did! Fumu-chan voted for her from the start!
あ、じゃあフムちゃん！
Ah, then Fumu-chan!
ミオしか勝たんって言ってたな。
They were saying "Mio is the best".
言ってたー！レース開始したいと思います！
They were! Okay, let's start the race!
じゃあハコス、位置について用意してもらえる？
Alright Hakos, could you get ready on "On your marks"?
え、待って！これ被ってたらどうなるんですか？
Wait, what happens if our picks overlap?
私たちが勝った時に、またそこで殴り合いが発生するんですか？
If we win, do we have to fight each other for it?
いやいや、1位を当てた人全員に景品あげる！
No no, everyone who guessed 1st place gets a prize!
全員！？ならいいね！
Everyone?! That's great then!
それでは...ミオちゃんも怪我しないように準備してねー！
Alright then... Mio-chan, get ready so you don't hurt yourself!
走る準備はできてます！行けるぞミオ！
I'm ready to run! You can do it, Mio!
犬、赤い線に準備しました！
The dogs are set at the red line!
位置について、よーい...スタート！
On your marks, get set... Go!
行け行け！
Go, go!
4番！行け！
Number 4! Go!
ミオ先輩！がんばれ！
Mio-senpai! Do your best!
行け！行け！行け！
Go! Go! Go!
がんばれ！がんばれ！
Keep going! Keep going!
おー！ゴール！
Woah! Finish!
え？これどうなったの？
Huh? What happened?
ミオさんとー、よーい同時に？
Mio-san and... at the exact same time?
ミオちゃんが死んだ！ミオちゃーん！
Mio-chan died! Mio-chan!
ミオと4の差で...
It's between Mio and Number 4...
ミオ先輩、もう一回走れますか？
Mio-senpai, can you run one more time?
倒れてますけど！ミオちゃん大丈夫ー！？
She's collapsed! Mio-chan, are you okay?!
4番とタイですね。
It's a tie with Number 4.
ねえねえ、もう走りたくない...
Hey... I don't want to run anymore...
走りたくないよ！
I don't wanna run!
走らないだけ...無理だろ！
You just don't run... That's impossible!
絶対4番の方が有利だろ！
Number 4 definitely has the advantage!
4番体力使ってないからね。
Because Number 4 hasn't used up any stamina.
ラスト！ラスト！
Last time! Last time!
行けるぞミオ！
You got this, Mio!
みなさん、もう一回4番だと思う人手あげてください！
Everyone, raise your hand if you think Number 4 will win this time!
Who thinks number 4 is gonna win? They're doing it one more time.
あれ？もこちゃん？
Huh? Moko-chan?
機械だからと思って...
I thought because it's a machine...
じゃあ4番の人、はい！
Okay, those for Number 4, raise your hand!
スバル、ねねち、こより...
Subaru, Nenechi, Koyori...
じゃあそのほか、ミオちゃんね。
Okay, everyone else goes to Mio-chan.
待って！助けてよ！
Wait! Help me!
じゃああの、1分休憩で！
Alright then, 1-minute break!
ストレッチ！ストレッチ！
Stretch! Stretch!
がんばって！がんばって！
Do your best! Do your best!
まさか過酷になるとは思わんやん！
Who knew it'd be this harsh?!
あんなキラキラした目で勝てるって語ってたじゃないか！
You were talking about winning with such sparkling eyes earlier!
こんな走ると思わんかった！がんばれミオちゃん！
I didn't think I'd run this much! Hang in there, Mio-chan!
元々この企画ミオちゃん考案だから自業自得やんけ！
Mio-chan came up with this event originally, so it's your own fault!
責任持って走れ！
Take responsibility and run!
犬のヘビが...
The dog's snake...
なんか言ってる...
Saying something...
Look at this! おー！超動いてる！
Look at this! Woah! It's moving so much!
今ね、ミオちゃんが休憩してる間にね...
Right now, while Mio-chan is taking a break...
ミオちゃん、大丈夫ー？
Mio-chan, are you okay?
大丈夫、今ね、ビブーがね、新技を開発したから
It's fine. Biboo just developed a new ultimate move.
はあ？
Huh?
ここで、ねねちの開発した新技を見てレースに行きたいと思います！
Now, let's watch Nene-chi's new ultimate move before heading into the race!
行くよ。ミオちゃん見てて画面。応援してるからみんな。せーの！
Here we go. Mio-chan, watch the screen. Everyone's cheering! Ready, set...
はーーー！
Haaaa!
え、地味だな。なんか想像より...
Eh, that's pretty plain. Somehow, compared to what I imagined...
じゃ終わり！はい、再開してください！
Alright, that's it! Okay, please resume!
じゃじゃーん！ミオちゃん！
Tada! Mio-chan!
やってくれたなー！やってくれたなー！
You really did it! You really did it!
大丈夫、ミオちゃん、始めるよ！
It's okay, Mio-chan, we're starting!
それじゃあ、始めるよ！
Alright then, let's start!
じゃあ、よーい、スタートで走ってくださいよ！
Alright, please start running on "Ready, set, go!"
じゃあ、4対4 VS ミオちゃんです！それでは参ります！
So it's 4-on-4 VS Mio-chan! Here we go!
よーい、スタート！
Ready, start!
ということで、勝者ミオちゃん！ミオちゃん、インタビュー、インタビュー！
And so, the winner is Mio-chan! Mio-chan, time for an interview, an interview!
すごい！今のお気持ちは1位で...
Amazing! How do you feel about coming in 1st place...
死ぬ...
I'm gonna die...
自分で企画した企画で死ぬってどういうことですかこれ？
What does it mean to die in a stream event you planned yourself?!
とんでもない企画です
This is an absurd event plan.
はい、ということで、1位になったミオちゃんに予想した人はですね、後で...
Alright, so for those who guessed Mio-chan would win 1st place...
Appleカード...
Apple Gift Cards...
ええーー？！
Ehhh?!
プレゼントしますので...
We will present them to you, so...
もらえない...
I don't get one...
電子レンジで調理しました！
I cooked it in the microwave!
何これ、グミ？グミです！
What's this, gummies? They're gummies!
食べてみてください！横はポテトらしい
Please try it! On the side is potato, apparently.
すごい！チーズだから美味しい！
Amazing! Since it's cheese, it's delicious!
いただきまーす！
Thanks for the food!
まずいですー！まずい！
It tastes terrible! Terrible!
水！水！水！水！
Water! Water! Water! Water!
みこち先輩！はい、ピザが出来上がりました！
Mikochi-senpai! Here, the pizza is ready!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ソーセージは長ッ！
The sausage is so long!
愛情込めましたから！
Because I put lots of love into it!
いただきます！
Thanks for the food!
うわ、やばい！
Whoa, oh no!
熱い 熱いよね？ 熱々
It's hot, isn't it? Piping hot!
イキイキイキ...
Fresh, fresh, fresh...
One bite! One bite!
本当ですか？
Really?
美味しいね！ Yum yum!
Delicious! Yum yum!
Really?
ガチャで60万円で...
Spending 600,000 yen on gacha...
ざっけんな！
Are you kidding me?!
参加賞です。
It's a participation prize.
あ、でもキャンディ入ってないね。
Ah, but there's no candy in it.
参加賞？！ 60万じゃねぇよ！
Participation prize?! Not for 600,000 yen!
60万じゃねぇよ！
Not for 600,000 yen!
それじゃ締めましょうか、そろそろ。
Well then, shall we wrap this up soon?
助けてー！
Help me!
本日はありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for today!
楽しかったです！
It was so much fun!
それじゃせっかくなんでね、今日ね、お店屋さんしてくれた、まずフブちゃん、どうでしたか今日は？
So since we're here, first off, Fubu-chan, who ran a stall today, how was it today?
楽しかったワン！ 犬です！ キュ〜
It was fun, woof! I'm a dog! Kyu~
楽しかったワンです！
It was fun, woof!
はい、ありがとうございます。
Yes, thank you very much.
じゃあ、あの夏祭り主催に対してハコスどうですか？
So, Hakos, how about towards the host of the summer festival?
ねぇ、そのさ、食べるのやめて！
Hey, stop eating that!
助かったー！ ありがとうございましたー！
That saved me! Thank you so much!
じゃあそして、走った…ワンちゃんミオしゃ、どうでしたか今日は？
And next, Mio-sha, who ran around like a dog, how was it today?
たくさんの人が来てくれて、すごく嬉しかったですわ。
Lots of people came, so I was really happy.
あ、よかったですわ！ じゃあ締めということで、ありがとうございましたー！
Ah, that's great! So to wrap up, thank you very much!
それじゃ最後は「おつホロ夏祭り」で終わりたいと思います！
Then finally, I'd like to end with "Otsu Holo Summer Festival"!
それではいきましょう、せーの！
Alright, here we go! Ready, set...
おつホロ夏祭り〜！
Otsu Holo Summer Festival~!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
チャンネル登録、高評価お願いします！
Subscribe and like my channel!